const gkQuiz = [
    {
      question: `What is the largest planet in our solar system?
        a: Earth
        b: Jupiter
        c: Mars
        d: Venus`,
      correctAnswer: "b",
    },
    {
      question: `Who wrote 'Romeo and Juliet'?
        a: Charles Dickens
        b: Jane Austen
        c: William Shakespeare
        d: Mark Twain`,
      correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
      question: `What is the capital of Japan?
        a: Tokyo
        b: Beijing
        c: Seoul
        d: Bangkok`,
      correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
      question: `Which planet is known as the Red Planet?
        a: Venus
        b: Mercury
        c: Jupiter
        d: Mars`,
      correctAnswer: "d",
    },
    {
      question: `Who painted the Mona Lisa?
        a: Vincent van Gogh
        b: Leonardo da Vinci
        c: Pablo Picasso
        d: Claude Monet`,
      correctAnswer: "b",
    },
    {
      question: `What is the currency of Australia?
        a: Euro
        b: Yen
        c: Dollar
        d: Pound`,
      correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
      question: `In which year did the Titanic sink?
        a: 1912
        b: 1920
        c: 1905
        d: 1931`,
      correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
      question: `Who developed the theory of relativity?
        a: Isaac Newton
        b: Galileo Galilei
        c: Stephen Hawking
        d: Albert Einstein`,
      correctAnswer: "d",
    },
    {
      question: `What is the capital of Brazil?
        a: Rio de Janeiro
        b: Brasília
        c: São Paulo
        d: Buenos Aires`,
      correctAnswer: "b",
    },
    {
      question: `Which element has the chemical symbol 'O'?
        a: Oxygen
        b: Gold
        c: Silver
        d: Iron`,
      correctAnswer: "a",
    },
];

module.exports = gkQuiz;